A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, China Medical Board records, RG 4 FA114
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1913-1929; 1
  - Appropriations - Alphabetical, 1919-1929; 2
    - Public Health, 1919-23 (Box 78, Folder 1804)
    - Public Health, 1919-23 (Box 78, Folder 1805)
    - Public Health Nursing, 1921 (Box 78, Folder 1806)
      Hookworm, literature, physical education, Central Epidemic Prevention Bureau, field work stations, Ministry of Health, political situation, student unrest, medical and Pre-medical education, quarantine, Chinese reparations, education, TB, soil sanitation, fellowships.
    - Publications, 1926-28 (Box 78, Folder 1807)
    - Putsi Hospital, 1922-25 (Box 78, Folder 1808)
    - Radio Corporation of America (Box 78, Folder 1809)
    - Dr. Ramsey, 1924 (Box 78, Folder 1810)
    - Walter E. Ranger, 1922 (Box 78, Folder 1811)
    - W. C. Rappleye, 1923 (Box 78, Folder 1812)
    - Reconstruction Nospital, 1923 (Box 78, Folder 1813)
    - Red Cross General Hospital - Shanghai, 1922-28 (Box 78, Folder 1814)
    - Red Cross Society - Shanghai, 1922 (Box 78, Folder 1815)
    - Reformed Church in America, 1919-27 (Box 78, Folder 1816)
    - Reformed Church Mission Hospital - Amoy, 1923-27 (Box 78, Folder 1817)
    - Reformed Church Mission Hospital - Shenchowfu, 1919-20 (Box 78, Folder 1818)
    - Reformed Church Mission Hospital - Siokhe, 1921-25 (Box 78, Folder 1819)
    - Reformed Presbyterian Church, 1922 (Box 78, Folder 1820)
    - J. Christie Reid, 1921 (Box 78, Folder 1821)
    - Henry O. Reik, 1922 (Box 78, Folder 1822)
    - Paul Reinsch, 1919-22 (Box 78, Folder 1823)
    - Report on Discussion, Meeting of China Medical Board, April 12, 1923 (Box 78, Folder 1824)
    - Report of Resident Director, 1919-23 (Box 78, Folder 1825)
    - Resident Director, 1919-21 (Box 79, Folder 1826)
      Cross-references, duplication of subject material; political situation, education, CMB administration and general policy, fellowships, PUMC property and construction, indemnity fnds, mission hospitals, summer institute, Sino-Japanese relations, Pan-Pacific Congress, public health, research, immigration, foreign policy, exchange, famine relief, narcotics.
    - Resident Director, 1919-21 (Box 79, Folder 1827)
    - Resident Director, 1919-21 (Box 79, Folder 1828)
    - Resident Director, 1919-21 (Box 79, Folder 1829)
    - Resident Director, 1919-21 (Box 79, Folder 1830)
    - Resident Director, 1919-21 (Box 79, Folder 1831)
    - Resident Director, 1919-21 (Box 79, Folder 1832)
    - Resident Director, 1919-21 (Box 79, Folder 1833)
    - Resident Director, 1919-21 (Box 79, Folder 1834)
    - Resident Director, 1919-21 (Box 79, Folder 1835)
    - Resident Director, 1922-April 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1836)
    - Resident Director, 1922-April 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1837)
    - Resident Director, 1922-April 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1838)
    - Resident Director, 1922-April 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1839)
    - Resident Director, 1922-April 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1840)
    - Resident Director, 1922-April 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1841)
    - Resident Director, 1922-April 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1842)
    - Resident Director, 1922-April 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1843)
    - Resident Director, 1922-April 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1844)
    - Resident Director, 1922-April 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1845)
    - Resident Director, May 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 1846)
    - Resident Director, May 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 1847)
    - Resident Director, May 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 1848)
    - Resident Director, May 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 1849)
    - Resident Director, May 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 1850)
    - Resident Director, May 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 1851)
    - Resident Director, May 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 1852)
    - Resident Director, May 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 1853)
    - Resident Director, May 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 1854)
    - Resident Director, May 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 1855)
    - Resident Director, 1927 (Box 82, Folder 1856)
    - Resident Director, 1927 (Box 82, Folder 1857)
    - Rhode Island Health Department, 1924-25 (Box 82, Folder 1858)
    - Rhode Island Hospital, 1922-24 (Box 82, Folder 1859)
    - A. L. Richards, 1923 (Box 82, Folder 1860)
    - C. S. Richardson, 1923 (Box 82, Folder 1860)
    - George L. Richards, 1920 (Box 82, Folder 1861)
    - W. S. Richardson, 1919-27 (Box 82, Folder 1863)
    - Edward Rieha, 1919-24 (Box 82, Folder 1864)
    - Theordora Rhodes, 1925-27 (Box 82, Folder 1865)
    - Rochester General Hospital, 1928 (Box 82, Folder 1866)
    - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1919-28 (Box 82, Folder 1867)
    - Rockefeller Institute, 1919-28 (Box 82, Folder 1868)
    - Rockefeller Institute, 1919-28 (Box 82, Folder 1869)
    - Roosevelt Hospital, 1923 (Box 82, Folder 1870)
    - Wickliffe Rose, 1920-27 (Box 82, Folder 1871)
    - William C. Ross, 1922-23 (Box 82, Folder 1872)
    - Royal Anthropological Institute, 1925 (Box 82, Folder 1873)
    - Royal Society, 1927 (Box 82, Folder 1874)
    - Albert Ruddock, 1922-23 (Box 82, Folder 1875)
    - Beardsley Ruml, 1923-27 (Box 82, Folder 1876)
    - F. F. Russell, 1922-25 (Box 82, Folder 1877)
    - Josephine Russell, 1920 (Box 82, Folder 1878)
    - Russell Sage Foundation, 1919-21 (Box 82, Folder 1879)
    - Russia, 1927 (Box 82, Folder 1880)
    - Russian Medical School, 1919 (Box 82, Folder 1881)
    - Martin Ryerson, 1922 (Box 82, Folder 1882)
    - F. R. Sabin, 1927-28 (Box 82, Folder 1883)
    - St. Luke's International Hospital - Tokyo, 1922-23 (Box 82, Folder 1884)
    - Salaries, 1924-27 (Box 82, Folder 1885)
    - Clarence Salsbury, 1919 (Box 82, Folder 1886)
    - Salt Gabelle, 1922-23 (Box 82, Folder 1887)
    - Alden Sampson, 1922 (Box 82, Folder 1888)
    - Sanatorium School for Girls, 1919-20 (Box 82, Folder 1889)
    - Shinjiro Sato, 1923 (Box 82, Folder 1890)
    - Mr. Schaumloeffel, 1922-23 (Box 82, Folder 1891)
    - W. M. Schultz, 1919-25 (Box 82, Folder 1892)
    - Science, 1924 (Box 82, Folder 1893)
    - Science Society of China, 1924-27 (Box 82, Folder 1894)
    - Scripps Institute, 1927 (Box 82, Folder 1895)
    - Secretaries, 1921-27 (Box 82, Folder 1896)
    - Seventh Day Adventist Mision, 1922-27 (Box 82, Folder 1897)
    - Severance Union Medical College - Seoul, 1923-25 (Box 82, Folder 1898)
    - Shanghai American School, 1919-25 (Box 82, Folder 1899)
    - Shanghai General Hospital, 1924-25 (Box 82, Folder 1900)
    - Shanghai Medical School, 1919-26 (Box 83, Folder 1901)
    - Shanghai Property Owners Association, 1927 (Box 83, Folder 1902)
    - Shanghai Purchasing Agency, 1919-21 (Box 83, Folder 1903)
    - Shanghai Sanitarium, 1922-23 (Box 83, Folder 1904)
    - Shanghai Union Medical College, 1927-28 (Box 83, Folder 1905)
    - Shanghai Union Medical College, 1927-28 (Box 83, Folder 1906)
    - Shanghai Union Medical College, 1927-28 (Box 83, Folder 1907)
    - Shanghai Union Medical College for Women, 1919-27 (Box 83, Folder 1908)
    - Shantung Road Hospital, 1925 (Box 83, Folder 1909)
    - J. L. Shen, 1927 (Box 83, Folder 1910)
    - Hsi Chiao Sheng, 1919 (Box 83, Folder 1911)
    - L. L. Shew, 1921-25 (Box 83, Folder 1912)
    - Gerald Shibley, 1919 (Box 83, Folder 1913)
    - Vincent Shibusawa, 1922-23 (Box 83, Folder 1914)
    - Dr. Shields, 1921 (Box 83, Folder 1915)
    - K. Shiga, 1926-27 (Box 83, Folder 1916)
    - K. Shiino, 1928 (Box 83, Folder 1917)
    - Siamese Scholarships, 1921-22 (Box 83, Folder 1918)
    - Dr. Sibley, 1925 (Box 83, Folder 1919)
    - T. E. Simmang, 1925 (Box 83, Folder 1920)
    - J. E. Skinner, 1925-28 (Box 83, Folder 1921)
    - Smith College, 1924 (Box 83, Folder 1922)
    - C. K. Snapper, 1928 (Box 83, Folder 1923)
    - Society for the Propagation of the Gospel in Foreign Parts, 1924-26 (Box 83, Folder 1924)
    - South Manchuria Medical College, 1924 (Box 83, Folder 1925)
    - South Manchuria Railway, 1923-28 (Box 83, Folder 1926)
    - Southeastern University, 1921-22 (Box 83, Folder 1927)
    - Robert F. Souther, 1921 (Box 83, Folder 1928)
    - William E. Souter, 1922 (Box 83, Folder 1929)
    - Frederick Spaulding, 1919 (Box 83, Folder 1930)
    - Sprue, 1924-25 (Box 84, Folder 1931)
    - Margaret Squibb, 1923 (Box 84, Folder 1932)
    - Frank Staley, 1922-25 (Box 84, Folder 1933)
    - Standard Oil Company, 1919-25 (Box 84, Folder 1934)
    - Stanford University, 1923-28 (Box 84, Folder 1935)
    - State Normal School, 1926 (Box 84, Folder 1936)
    - Milton Stauffer, 1920 (Box 84, Folder 1937)
    - Theodore Stebbins, 1924 (Box 84, Folder 1938)
    - Helen Sterling, 1922 (Box 84, Folder 1939)
    - F. W. Stevens, 1921-24 (Box 84, Folder 1940)
    - J. Steiglitz, 1919 (Box 84, Folder 1941)
    - Twenchih Stone, 1920-21 (Box 84, Folder 1942)
    - Stone and Webster, 1925-28 (Box 84, Folder 1943)
      PUMC Construction
    - Stone and Webster, 1925-28 (Box 84, Folder 1944)
    - Frederick Strauss, 1922-26 (Box 84, Folder 1945)
    - Richard Strong, 1923 (Box 84, Folder 1946)
    - Strong Memorial Hospital, 1927 (Box 84, Folder 1947)
    - E. B. Struthers, 1919 (Box 84, Folder 1948)
    - Student Relief Fund Committee, 1927 (Box 84, Folder 1949)
    - Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions, 1921-28 (Box 84, Folder 1950)
    - Summer Institute, 1923-25 (Box 84, Folder 1951)
      Science teacher education
    - Summer Institute, 1923-25 (Box 84, Folder 1952)
    - Summer Institute, 1923-25 (Box 84, Folder 1953)
    - Summer Institute, 1923-25 (Box 84, Folder 1954)
    - Summer Institute, 1923-25 (Box 84, Folder 1955)
    - The Sun and New York Herald, 1919-20 (Box 84, Folder 1956)
    - Sun Yat Sen University, 1927-28 (Box 84, Folder 1957)
    - Mme. Sun Yat Sen, 1927 (Box 84, Folder 1958)
    - F. T. Sung, 1919-23 (Box 84, Folder 1959)
    - Tshang Sung, 1925-26 (Box 84, Folder 1960)
    - Swan-Myers Company, 1928 (Box 84, Folder 1961)
    - Swarthmore College, 1925-26 (Box 84, Folder 1962)
    - Mrs. T. E. Sweet, 1924 (Box 84, Folder 1963)
    - Alfonso Sycip, 1919 (Box 84, Folder 1964)
    - Alfred Sao-Ke Sze, 1920 (Box 84, Folder 1965)
    - T. Philip Sze, 1920-27 (Box 84, Folder 1966)
    - Zing Ling Tai, 1927 (Box 85, Folder 1967)
    - K. K. Tan, 1924-25 (Box 85, Folder 1968)
    - Er Ho Tang, 1921-24 (Box 85, Folder 1969)
    - Mr. Tanimura, 1927 (Box 85, Folder 1970)
    - Shan Ming Tao, 1926-28 (Box 85, Folder 1971)
    - Sidney Tay, 1922 (Box 85, Folder 1972)
    - Gushue Taylor, 1919 (Box 85, Folder 1973)
    - Jospeh Taylor, 1923 (Box 85, Folder 1974)
    - Teachers Insurance Annuity Association, 1925-26 (Box 85, Folder 1975)
    - Shih K'on Teng, 1922-26 (Box 85, Folder 1976)
    - Terminology Committee, 1919-25 (Box 85, Folder 1977)
      Medical and scientific terminology
    - Theatre, 1928 (Box 85, Folder 1978)
    - Thomas Mott Osborne Memorial, 1927 (Box 85, Folder 1979)
    - H. J. Thorkelson, 1927 (Box 85, Folder 1980)
    - Robert Ting, 1925 (Box 85, Folder 1981)
    - V. K. Ting, 1921-27 (Box 85, Folder 1982)
    - Tokyo Imperial University, 1927-28 (Box 85, Folder 1983)
    - Tokyo School for Foreign Children, 1919 (Box 85, Folder 1984)
    - Chen Lang Tong, 1922 (Box 85, Folder 1985)
    - Tooker Memorial Hospital, 1926-28 (Box 85, Folder 1986)
    - Toronto General Hospital, 1922-28 (Box 85, Folder 1987)
    - Training Service, 1922-24 (Box 85, Folder 1988)
    - Translation of Medical Books, 1919-27 (Box 85, Folder 1989)
    - Zok Tsung Tsao, 1919 (Box 85, Folder 1990)
    - Tsing Hua College, 1919-28 (Box 85, Folder 1991)
      Student unrest, political situation, secondary education
    - Tsing Hua College, 1919-28 (Box 85, Folder 1992)
    - Tsing Hua College, 1919-28 (Box 85, Folder 1993)
    - Tsing Hua College, 1919-28 (Box 85, Folder 1994)
    - Tsing Hua College, 1919-28 (Box 85, Folder 1995)
    - Tsing Tao University, 1924 (Box 86, Folder 1996)
    - Thelma Tsong, 1927-28 (Box 86, Folder 1997)
    - Tsu Yee Institute, 1925 (Box 86, Folder 1998)
    - Tsuda College, 1924-25 (Box 86, Folder 1999)
    - Sr. Tu, 1928 (Box 86, Folder 2000)
    - Charles H. Tuck, 1922-27 (Box 86, Folder 2001)
    - Tufts College, 1927-28 (Box 86, Folder 2002)
    - Tulane University, 1924-28 (Box 86, Folder 2003)
    - Tung Chi College, 1922-27 (Box 86, Folder 2004)
    - Tungchow North China American School, 1922-26 (Box 86, Folder 2005)
    - Tung Teh Hospital, 1926 (Box 86, Folder 2006)
    - Dorsey Tyler, 1921 (Box 86, Folder 2007)
    - Union College, 1922-27 (Box 86, Folder 2008)
    - Union Theological Seminary, 1925 (Box 86, Folder 2009)
    - Union Brethren in Christ, 1920-24 (Box 86, Folder 2010)
    - Union Brethren Mission Hospital - Siu Lam, 1923 (Box 86, Folder 2011)
    - United Christian Missionary Society, 1923-28 (Box 86, Folder 2012)
    - United Christian Mission Hospital - Luchowfu, 1920-28 (Box 86, Folder 2013)
    - United Christian Mission Hospital - Luchowfu, 1920-28 (Box 86, Folder 2014)
    - United Christian Mission Hospital - Luchowfu, 1920-28 (Box 86, Folder 2015)
    - United Christian Mission Hospital - Nantungchow, 1920-28 (Box 86, Folder 2016)
      Political situation, x-ray, fellowships
    - United Christian Mission Hospital - Nantungchow, 1920-28 (Box 86, Folder 2017)
    - United Church of Canada, 1926-28 (Box 86, Folder 2018)
    - United Engineering Society, 1922-23 (Box 86, Folder 2019)
    - United Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1921-23 (Box 86, Folder 2020)
    - United Evangelical Mission Hospital - Leling, 1920-22 (Box 86, Folder 2021)
    - United Free Church of Scotland, 1925-26 (Box 87, Folder 2022)
    - United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Hulan, 1921-22 (Box 87, Folder 2023)
    - United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Moukden, 1919-27 (Box 87, Folder 2024)
    - United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Moukden, 1919-27 (Box 87, Folder 2025)
    - United Fruit Company, 1924 (Box 87, Folder 2026)
    - United Lutheran Mission - Sinyangchow, 1926 (Box 87, Folder 2027)
    - United States, 1919-28 (Box 87, Folder 2028)
      Government departments including Immigration, Customs, Public Health Service, Commerce, Education and State.
    - United States, 1919-28 (Box 87, Folder 2029)
    - United States, 1919-28 (Box 87, Folder 2030)
    - Universite l'Aurore, 1923-26 (Box 87, Folder 2031)
    - University of Alabama, 1927 (Box 87, Folder 2032)
    - University of California, 1921-26 (Box 87, Folder 2033)
    - University of Chicago, 1919-28 (Box 87, Folder 2034)
    - University of Chicago, 1919-28 (Box 87, Folder 2035)
    - University of Cincinnati, 1920-24 (Box 87, Folder 2036)
    - University College, 1922-26 (Box 87, Folder 2037)
    - University of Denver, 1922-24 (Box 87, Folder 2038)
    - University of Edinburgh, 1921-22 (Box 87, Folder 2039)
    - University of Hawaii, 1926 (Box 87, Folder 2040)
    - University of Hong Kong, 1920-28 (Box 87, Folder 2041)
    - University of Hong Kong, 1920-28 (Box 87, Folder 2042)
    - University of Illinois, 1919-27 (Box 87, Folder 2043)
    - University of Iowa, 1921-27 (Box 87, Folder 2044)
    - University of Irkutsk, 1921-22 (Box 87, Folder 2045)
    - University of Louisville, 1920-22 (Box 88, Folder 2046)
    - University of Michigan, 1921-28 (Box 88, Folder 2047)
    - University of Minnesota, 1919-28 (Box 88, Folder 2048)
    - University of Nanking, 1919-28 (Box 88, Folder 2049)
      Political situation, Boxer Indemnity, anti-foreign feeling, pre-medical education, agricultural college, visiting professors, buildings, exchange, fellowships, science education, China Famine Fund.
    - University of Nanking, 1919-28 (Box 88, Folder 2050)
    - University of Nanking, 1919-28 (Box 88, Folder 2051)
    - University of Nanking, 1919-28 (Box 88, Folder 2052)
    - University of Nanking, 1919-28 (Box 88, Folder 2053)
    - University of Nanking, 1919-28 (Box 88, Folder 2054)
    - University of Nanking, 1919-28 (Box 88, Folder 2055)
    - University of Nanking, 1919-28 (Box 88, Folder 2056)
    - University of Nanking, 1919-28 (Box 88, Folder 2057)
    - University of Nanking Hospital, 1923-28 (Box 89, Folder 2058)
    - University of Nanking Hospital, 1923-28 (Box 89, Folder 2059)
    - University of Oregon, 1922-25 (Box 89, Folder 2060)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1919-28 (Box 89, Folder 2061)
    - University of Rochester, 1920 (Box 89, Folder 2062)
    - University of Sophia, 1921 (Box 89, Folder 2063)
    - University of Strasbourg, 1922 (Box 89, Folder 2064)
    - University of Texas, 1922-27 (Box 89, Folder 2065)
    - University of Tokyo, 1924 (Box 89, Folder 2066)
    - University of Toledo, 1924-25 (Box 89, Folder 2067)
    - University of Toronto, 1919-28 (Box 89, Folder 2068)
    - University of Vienna, 1924 (Box 89, Folder 2069)
    - University of Warsaw, 1923 (Box 89, Folder 2070)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1919-27 (Box 89, Folder 2071)
    - University of Zurich, 1924 (Box 89, Folder 2072)
    - Vanderbuilt in China, 1920 (Box 89, Folder 2073)
    - Vanderbuilt University, 1922-28 (Box 89, Folder 2074)
    - Louis Versiglia, 1926 (Box 89, Folder 2075)
    - George E. Vincent, 1919-26 (Box 89, Folder 2076)
    - George E. Vincent, 1919-26 (Box 89, Folder 2077)
    - Visiting Professors, 1922-26 (Box 89, Folder 2078)
    - J. A. L. Waddell, 1924-25 (Box 89, Folder 2079)
    - Sam Wakefield, 1921 (Box 89, Folder 2080)
    - Guy M. Walker, 1919-20 (Box 89, Folder 2081)
    - Chu Chia Wong, 1925 (Box 89, Folder 2082)
    - Chen Tsai Wong, 1922 (Box 89, Folder 2083)
    - Chi Chen Wong, 1924-25 (Box 89, Folder 2084)
    - C. Y. Wong, 1919-20 (Box 89, Folder 2085)
    - Gwen Hsin Wong, 1919-20 (Box 89, Folder 2086)
    - P. K. Wong, 1925 (Box 89, Folder 2087)
    - Robert Wong, 1922-28 (Box 89, Folder 2088)
    - S. T. Wong, 1922 (Box 89, Folder 2089)
    - T. S. Wong, 1921-26 (Box 89, Folder 2090)
    - Y. C. Wong, 1926 (Box 89, Folder 2091)
    - Y. C. Wong, 1924-25 (Box 90, Folder 2092)
    - Yu Mei Wong, 1927 (Box 90, Folder 2093)
    - Helen B. Ward, 1919 (Box 90, Folder 2094)
    - A. R. Warner, 1920 (Box 90, Folder 2095)
    - Langdon Warner, 1922-27 (Box 90, Folder 2096)
    - Washington Sanitarium, 1925 (Box 90, Folder 2097)
    - Washington University, 1919-27 (Box 90, Folder 2098)
    - Water Softening Plant, 1923-24 (Box 90, Folder 2099)
    - Water Supply, 1924 (Box 90, Folder 2100)
    - John G. Welch, 1924 (Box 90, Folder 2101)
    - Yu Cing Wen, 1922-24 (Box 90, Folder 2102)
    - Wesley College, 1927 (Box 90, Folder 2103)
    - Wesleyan Mission Hospital, 1927 (Box 90, Folder 2104)
    - West China Union University, 1919-28 (Box 90, Folder 2105)
      Translations, fellowships, political situation.
    - West China Union University, 1919-28 (Box 90, Folder 2106)
    - West China Union University, 1919-28 (Box 90, Folder 2107)
    - West China Union University, 1919-28 (Box 90, Folder 2108)
    - West China Union University, 1919-28 (Box 90, Folder 2109)
    - West China Union University, 1919-28 (Box 90, Folder 2110)
    - Western Hills Orphanage, 1921-22 (Box 90, Folder 2111)
    - Western Hills Tuberculosis Hospital, 1922-27 (Box 90, Folder 2112)
    - Western Reserve University, 1920-27 (Box 91, Folder 2113)
    - Western Returned Students Club, 1927 (Box 91, Folder 2114)
    - Western University, 1921-22 (Box 91, Folder 2115)
    - Anne Wharton, 1920 (Box 91, Folder 2116)
    - George C. Whipple, 1921-23 (Box 91, Folder 2117)
    - Benjamin White, 1923-25 (Box 91, Folder 2118)
    - Roberta White, 1925 (Box 91, Folder 2119)
    - S. E. Whitnald, 1924 (Box 91, Folder 2120)
    - Ray Lyman Wilbur, 1924 (Box 91, Folder 2121)
    - L. R. Wilfley, 1919 (Box 91, Folder 2122)
    - Willard Parker Hospital, 1926-27 (Box 91, Folder 2123)
    - Willard Straight Fund, 1924-26 (Box 91, Folder 2124)
    - Howard C. Williams, 1926 (Box 91, Folder 2125)
    - Howard J. Williams, 1922-23 (Box 91, Folder 2126)
    - Howard Y. Williams, 1919 (Box 91, Folder 2127)
    - Isaac N. Williams, 1922-23 (Box 91, Folder 2128)
    - Wilbur L. Williams, 1927 (Box 91, Folder 2129)
    - Williams College, 1925 (Box 91, Folder 2130)
    - E. B. Wilson, 1922 (Box 91, Folder 2131)
    - William Wirt, 1922 (Box 91, Folder 2132)
    - Wistar Institute, 1925-28 (Box 91, Folder 2133)
    - Ernst Witt, 1923 (Box 91, Folder 2134)
    - Women's American Baptist Foreign Missionary Society, 1920 (Box 91, Folder 2135)
    - Women's Christian College in the Orient, 1923 (Box 91, Folder 2136)
    - Women's Hospital, 1919 (Box 91, Folder 2137)
    - Women's Medical College of Pennsylvania, 1919-25 (Box 91, Folder 2138)
    - Women's Missionary Society, 1926 (Box 91, Folder 2139)
    - Women's Union Christian Colleges, 1921 (Box 91, Folder 2140)
    - S. Y. Wong, 1923-28 (Box 91, Folder 2141)
    - T. L. Wong, 1923 (Box 91, Folder 2142)
    - Z. T. K. Woo, 1919-22 (Box 91, Folder 2143)
    - Irving Wood, 1923 (Box 91, Folder 2144)
    - Ruth Wood, 1923 (Box 91, Folder 2145)
    - Arthur Woods, 1925-28 (Box 91, Folder 2146)
    - Robert A. Woods, 1919 (Box 91, Folder 2147)
    - C. W. Woodworth, 1923 (Box 91, Folder 2148)
    - The World, 1927 (Box 91, Folder 2149)
    - World Missionary Atlas, 1922 (Box 91, Folder 2150)
    - James Y. S. Wu, 1923 (Box 91, Folder 2151)
    - Lien Teh Wu, 1923-27 (Box 91, Folder 2152)
    - Mildred Wu, 1926 (Box 91, Folder 2153)
    - Tsit Ng Wu, 1927 (Box 91, Folder 2154)
    - X-ray Appropriations, 1922-23 (Box 91, Folder 2155)
    - Yale Club, 1919-22 (Box 91, Folder 2156)
    - Yale Missionary Society, 1919-28 (Box 91, Folder 2157)
    - Yale Missionary Society, 1919-28 (Box 91, Folder 2158)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2159)
      Political situation, strike, student unrest, pre-medical school and education, Chinese/American control of education, fellowships, indemnity, union universities, missionary societies, famine, buildings and equipment.
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2160)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2161)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2162)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2163)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2164)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2165)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2166)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2167)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2168)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1918-23 (Box 92, Folder 2169)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1924-October/November 1925 (Box 93, Folder 2170)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1924-October/November 1925 (Box 93, Folder 2171)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1924-October/November 1925 (Box 93, Folder 2172)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1924-October/November 1925 (Box 93, Folder 2173)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1924-October/November 1925 (Box 93, Folder 2174)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1924-October/November 1925 (Box 93, Folder 2175)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1924-October/November 1925 (Box 93, Folder 2176)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1924-October/November 1925 (Box 93, Folder 2177)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, 1924-October/November 1925 (Box 93, Folder 2178)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, December 1925-26 (Box 94, Folder 2179)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, December 1925-26 (Box 94, Folder 2180)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, December 1925-26 (Box 94, Folder 2181)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, December 1925-26 (Box 94, Folder 2182)